# Daiana Gusatu

Flat 51, 33-39 Bailey Wills Building, Talbot Road, NN1 4HZ, Northampton, UK +447947937696 | daiana.gusatu@gmail.com

# **PROFILE**

A highly motivated and hardworking individual, I am currently a second-year student enrolled in a Computing - Software Engineering course at the University of Northampton, UK. I am willing to prove outstanding technical and personal skills, currently developing knowledge in C++, having previous experience in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Java, SQL. My career goal is to become a fully-qualified and experienced software engineer/developer for a well-respected and market-leading company.

## **KEY ACHIEVEMENTS**

- Valedictorian in high school (2010-2014), final grade 9.75 / 10;
- I won a national competition organised by Erasmus with a project referred to the European Union by conceiving a law regarding student rights in Europe. I spent few days at the European Union Parliament in Strasbourg debating and doing projects with students all over Europe;
- I took 4th place at the nationals for Theory in Sports, grade 9.60 / 10;
- As a leader of my school I spent one week in Jaen (Spain) living with a local family where I had numerous activities at the local school.

# **EDUCATION & QUALIFICATIONS**

- University of Northampton BSc Computing Software Engineering (ongoing);
- Sports Highschool 23 subjects studied in 4 years with grade 10 each (maximum);
- Romanian Baccalaureate 8.38.

## **KEY SKILLS**

#### Communication skills

- Excellent written and verbal communication skills (Romanian and English);
- Speaking in public, to groups of 20-1000 people (e.g. different projects at both European Parliaments, teaching, conferences, etc);

#### Organizational / managerial skills

- Leadership abilities (gained after managing lots of groups and running team projects);
- Professionalism (never skipped a day out of work);
- Team player;
- Ability to prioritize independently;
- Effective multitasking;

## Job-related skills

- HTML, CSS, Java, SQL;
- Event planning;
- Mathematics.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## **Junior Technical Consultant | Pragmatiq Solutions**

Dec 2019 to Ongoing

PragmatiQ Solutions is a Microsoft Dynamics Partner and leading professional services company, supporting clients ranging from small businesses to medium-sized enterprises. They focus on Customer Management (CRM), using the industry-leading Microsoft suite of business applications - Microsoft Dynamics 365.

- Configuration and customisation whilst implementing Microsoft Dynamics 365 CRM software;
- Supporting the pre-sales process in areas such as demonstrations & research and post-sales, as part of a Support Helpdesk Offering whilst being involved with a variety of client projects;
- Working on the internal development projects.

## **Sports and Leisure Assistant | School Lettings Solutions**

Nov 2018 to Dec 2019

School Lettings Solutions is a fast-growing company with the mission to be the largest provider of Sport and Leisure facilities in the UK focusing on Schools, community and the customer experience.

- Test the pool water for chlorine, PH, legionella, etc.;
- Make sure the sites are ready for the next day/booking, lock and secure the buildings;
- Attend meetings and train new employees.

## Au Pair | Cultural Care Au Pair

Aug 2017 to Aug 2018

Cultural Care is an agency based in multiple countries around the world, offering the opportunity to young people to live with an American host family for a year and care for their children.

- Helping with homework, driving the children to different play areas, camps, etc.
- Achievements: Cultural exchange; Improvement of creativity, responsibility, patience, adaptability;
- Team leader;
- · Organizational skills.

## ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Training: - Diploma in Accounting and Finance Level 4;

Certificate in Wedding and Event Planning Level 3;

Languages - Romanian, some French, Italian.

## **INTERESTS**

- Sports I played handball for 9 years winning multiple competitions, highest achievement being 10th place at the nationals;
- Travelling Visited over 20 countries and 200 cities;
- President of Metal Society:
- Vice-President of Vegan Social Club;
- Part of Game Changers Society;
- Part of Romanian Society;
- Part of Computing Society;
- Music Playing drums and writing music/lyrics;
- Coding.